once an hour, good afternoon, yes, where will I be
раз в час добрый день да откуда будете я
from Ukraine, the city of Khmelnitsky, the
из украины города хмельницкий
elector, the Bashkiria themselves on the
выборщика сами башкирии на
head of the forest, you look, I ask people from
башке лесу вы посмотрите я у людей из
Russia how you feel about the
россии спрашивать как вы относитесь к
war in Ukraine,
войне на украине
I think that this is a question and it is desirable to
я думаю что это вопрос и желательно
ask the moment why,
спрашивал момент почему
well, people are different and
ну люди бывают разные и
well
ну
if you say it might be wrong,
если вы скажем то может быть неправильно
let’s say you can judge correctly you can
скажем уж можешь правильно судить можно
blogger yes I’m a blogger I’m just
блогер да я блогер я просто я и
asking because I collect different
спрашиваю потому что я собираю разные
opinions of different people who is for who against
мнения разных людей кто за кто против
why for zaz and
почему за заз а
why are you for the war in Ukraine the
почему вы за войну в украине
DPR people are the fraternal Bashkir  but
днр ский народ это братский башкирском а
look here, I
вот смотрите вот я
see that you live in rich Russia as
вижу что вы живете в богатой россии как
rich in oil, diamonds, gas, but
богатые нефтью алмазами газом но что-то
something seems to be here, not quite a rich
у вас вот вроде тут не совсем богатая
house, so why,
хата такая так почему так
why, for example, in Ukraine, a village in
почему например в украине деревне в
Europe, a village is better, they don’t have gas,
европе деревне лучше у них нету газа
oil, why putin  doesn’t let you on the road
нефти почему путин не дает вам на дороге
[laughter]
[смех]
where did you buy the marble in the warehouse or where
где вы покупали мрамор на складе или где
I’m just wondering
меня просто интересно
what kind of marble you have
что там у вас какой
there too
то ли тоже с мрамора
can you show the toilet  it’s
можете показать туалет неинтересные
real and for the first time I see a dance on the
реально и первый раз вижу танец на
toilet
туалета
to hold a nifiga for myself
провести нифига себе
I won’t go there we
я не пойду туда
met to the end then marble men
встретились до конца то мрамор мужчины
cheat
обманываете
to the end to the end here is another path
до конца до конца вот еще дорожка
path path vision I saw you there you
дорожка vision я виделся там вы
end the marble path to the toilet and
кончается мраморная дорожка до туалета а
now we
сейчас мы
just haven’t changed
просто не поменял
I want to understand  the riddle why Putin is
я хочу понять загадку почему путин
robbing you, no, he takes his
грабит вас вот нет он забирает себе его
oligarchs money from gold, oil, diamonds,
олигархи деньги от золота нефти алмазов
and going to the wooden toilet to go and
а вывод в деревянный туалет ходить и
effort and
усилия и
money is your money Russian
деньги это же ваши деньги российские
troops,
войска
seriously, I can’t see it, show me
серьезно не могу я не видел покажите мне
where the sports roofs are at home,
где дома
I
спортом
don’t know, I’ll have to look
крыш не знаю надо будет посмотреть
it will
это будет
be different maybe different yes yes
может быть по другому по другому да да
tiles we have to divide the tiles as
черепица у нас на подели черепица как
always it
всегда было
would be a poor country we have no gas oil
бы бедная страна у нас нет газа нефти
diamonds gold and where does your
алмазов золото а куда же девается ваша
oil diamond gold go
нефть алмаза золото вот
oil births before
нефтяные рождения до
you have a rocket rocket to you what are our
вас есть ракета ракета к вам какие наши
taxes
налоги
vodka, too, you understand that your taxes
водку тоже вы понимаете что ваши налоги
fly in the form of our rockets to Ukraine,
летят в виде наших ракет в украину
but not in the form of your sewers in your
но не виде ваших канализации в вашем
village,
селе
but this  weapons
но это оружие
are considered
считаются
you are in a room in the house
вас есть в комнате в доме
there is a gas pipeline there is
есть газопровода есть
or was or
или был или
I can show it
могу показать
now I will show it here a
сейчас покажу вот тут
gas water
газовая колонка
heater like this
так apple то покажите плету что-то я не
this
укропчик мы тут этот
plumbing is at home
водопровод есть дома
until when everything is there we live cooler we are in
до когда все есть мы живем круче мы в
Europe you to pose a toilet what to the
европе you to pose a туалета чего в
toilet on the street
туалет на улице
but look only at in the garden you climb
но смотреть только на в огороде лазишь
but
да
you will not be at home with dirty hands behind the
ты же дома не будут грязными руками за
ass sit on the toilet
жопу садись на унитаз
we go to [ __ ]
мы идем по срали
we sat thought  we went home
посидели подумали домой зашли
an abortion at home there is also a toilet with a toilet
аборт дома тоже есть туалет с унитазом
there I think I don’t believe show yourself to the toilet
есть думаю я не верю покажитесь унитазу
they tell us that Russians don’t have toilets
нам говорят что у русских нет унитазов
on TV they say that Russians don’t have
по телеку говорят что у русских нет
toilets I’ll honestly head in the face as a result
унитазов я честно возглавлю в лицо итоге
no I showed you tegos on the
нет я тебя tegos показал на
street means there is no toilet at home and
улице значит нет унитаза дома и
then  let’s go to give in, I don’t understand how
потом идем на уступать я не понимаю как
I
бы я
would go abnormally somewhere
и пошел бы ненормально куда то
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
that you don’t deceive all this of ours you can
что вы не обманите все это нашего можно
trust wait a little and trust after
доверять подожди а чуть и доверие после
ha  ps
газы
showed show means sick of the
показали показать значит тошнит от
toilet
унитаза
showed well yes because he
показал ну да потому что у
doesn’t have
него нет
[music] a
[музыка]
promise is
обещание
just shorter no means no I’ll go
просто короче нет значит нет пойду
call I’ll show you well go let’s
позвоните покажу а ну идите давайте
[laughter]
[смех]
show the child an
покажет детстве штука
air raid alarm and in the bunker I can’t
воздушная тревога и в бункере не могу
go out
выходить
only the beeps of the bunker on which  there will be
лишь гудки бункере на каком будет
weights they called us to the bomb shelter but for
гиренок у нас позвали в бомбоубежище а
now wait for the bunker at least I can’t
пока жди бункер хотя бы не могу
we don’t matter poor country in the can
нас нет важно бедная страна в магазине
store without anything in the bunkers like
тазов без ничего в бункерах такие как
boys
пацаны
show me the bunker I’m not a fool
покажи мне бункер не я же не дурак
show me like what I have I
показываете походить что у меня есть
’ll show it
покажу это
if
если
you don’t  ashamed of the meaning of the year, I'll show you
вам не стыдно смысла году я тебе покажу
our flag, let's go, let's,
наш флаг давайте давайте давайте
what kind of
что это за
flag of the Ukrainian republic are you for Ukraine
флаг украинской республики вы за украину
before
до
work, these guys
работы эти пацаны
oh, we work as feasts
ой мы работаем пирами
[laugh]
[смех]
then that shells with a tray are there and unless
то что снаряды с подносом там и разве
everyone brings him a mug, so this
чтоб его все подносит кружку так вот это
will prove a  you are sniping we are so in the toilet you are
докажет а вы снайпинга мы так в туалете
really occupying so make sure to
реально занимаете вы поэтому убедитесь
show the toilet needs to you
показать унитаз нужд вам результаты
measures through the
о чем вытекает начались размер через
places of washing immediately came to my senses
места мойки
and
и
besides some characters on
кроме одни персонажи на
people
люди
live in such a hurry the river mine-off here
живут в такой спешке река майн оф тут
everyone is pumped out by him and his company all the
компания все
tournament resources and at the right moment I will
турнир сурс и и в нужную минуту
mark and even gifts fly away here to
размечу да и и подарки улетают тут в
ukraine a rocket on the
украину ракета на
terek and enough to study  the doctor is still a shame,
тереке а учебу хватающий врач еще обидно
but the Russians until you understand that
но русские пока вы не поймете что вас
your government is robbing you of all your
ваша власть грабит все ваши природные
natural resources;  super rich
ресурсы если россия т.к. супер богатая
all over europe sells resources so
всей европе продает ресурсы так то
why do you live so poor
почему вы живете вот так бедно
russia may with plast
россия мая с пласт
volin by birth will people don’t
волин родом воля люди не